[{
    "question_name": "Brain cancer",
    "question_detail": [
        {
            "1": {
                "question": "What is the definition of primary brain tumors?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Tumors that spread from other parts of the body",
                    "B": "Tumors that start in the brain",
                    "C": "Tumors that are formed in the spinal cord",
                    "D": "Tumors that occur in the cerebellum"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "2": {
                "question": "What is the most common type of primary brain tumor?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Meningioma",
                    "B": "Glioma",
                    "C": "Pineal gland tumor",
                    "D": "Pituitary gland tumor"
                },
                "correct_answer": "A"
            }
        },
        {
            "3": {
                "question": "What is the 10th leading cause of death for men and women?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Heart disease",
                    "B": "Brain and other nervous system cancer",
                    "C": "Lung cancer",
                    "D": "Leukemia"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "4": {
                "question": "What is the age group most affected by brain tumors?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Children and older adults",
                    "B": "Adults only",
                    "C": "Children only",
                    "D": "Older adults only"
                },
                "correct_answer": "A"
            }
        },
        {
            "5": {
                "question": "What is the gender that is more likely to develop a brain tumor?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Female",
                    "B": "Male",
                    "C": "Both are equally likely",
                    "D": "None of the above"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "6": {
                "question": "What is the effect of exposure to electromagnetic fields on the risk of developing a brain tumor?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Increases the risk",
                    "B": "Decreases the risk",
                    "C": "No link to an increased risk in adults",
                    "D": "Only increases the risk in children"
                },
                "correct_answer": "C"
            }
        },
        {
            "7": {
                "question": "What is the racial group that is more likely to develop gliomas?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Black",
                    "B": "White",
                    "C": "Asian",
                    "D": "Hispanic"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "8": {
                "question": "What is the source of N-nitroso compounds in the body?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Nitrites or nitrates found in some cured meats, cigarette smoke, and cosmetics",
                    "B": "Nitric oxide in the atmosphere",
                    "C": "Radon in homes",
                    "D": "Sulfur dioxide in air pollution"
                },
                "correct_answer": "A"
            }
        },
        {
            "9": {
                "question": "What are the 3 main parts of the brain?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Cerebrum, cerebellum, and spinal cord",
                    "B": "Cerebrum, cerebellum, and brain stem",
                    "C": "Cerebrum, spinal cord, and brain stem",
                    "D": "Cerebellum, spinal cord, and brain stem"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "10": {
                "question": "What is the function of the frontal lobe?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Controls vision",
                    "B": "Controls hearing",
                    "C": "Controls reasoning, emotions, problem-solving, expressive speech, and movement",
                    "D": "Controls sensation, touch, pain, and temperature"
                },
                "correct_answer": "C"
            }
        },
        {
            "11": {
                "question": "What is the layer of the meninges that is closest to the brain?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Dura mater",
                    "B": "Arachnoid",
                    "C": "Pia mater",
                    "D": "Meningeal layer"
                },
                "correct_answer": "C"
            }
        },
        {
            "12": {
                "question": "What is the source of the cerebrospinal fluid (CSF)?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Bloodstream",
                    "B": "Brain",
                    "C": "Spinal cord",
                    "D": "Near the center of the brain, in the lateral ventricles"
                },
                "correct_answer": "D"
            }
        },
        {
            "13": {
                "question": "What is the most common type of glioma?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Astrocytoma",
                    "B": "Oligodendroglioma",
                    "C": "Ependymoma",
                    "D": "Glioblastoma"
                },
                "correct_answer": "A"
            }
        },
        {
            "14": {
                "question": "What is the type of astrocytoma that is the most aggressive?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Grade I or pilocytic astrocytoma",
                    "B": "Grade II or low-grade diffuse astrocytoma",
                    "C": "Grade III or anaplastic astrocytoma",
                    "D": "Grade IV or glioblastoma"
                },
                "correct_answer": "D"
            }
        },
        {
            "15": {
                "question": "What is the type of tumor that starts in the meninges?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Glioma",
                    "B": "Meningioma",
                    "C": "Astrocytoma",
                    "D": "Pineal gland tumor"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "16": {
                "question": "What is the type of tumor that starts in the pineal gland?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Glioma",
                    "B": "Meningioma",
                    "C": "Astrocytoma",
                    "D": "Pineal gland tumor"
                },
                "correct_answer": "D"
            }
        },
        {
            "17": {
                "question": "What is the clinical presentation of brain tumors?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Seizures, headaches, and loss of vision",
                    "B": "Headaches, seizures, change in sensation, vision, smell, and/or hearing",
                    "C": "Loss of balance and difficulty with fine motor skills",
                    "D": "Personality or memory changes, nausea or vomiting, fatigue, drowsiness, sleep problems, memory problems"
                },
                "correct_answer": "B"
            }
        },
        {
            "18": {
                "question": "What is the method used to diagnose brain tumors?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "MRI, CT scan, PET-CT scan, lumbar puncture, myelogram, and molecular testing of the tumor",
                    "B": "Only MRI and CT scan",
                    "C": "Only PET-CT scan and lumbar puncture",
                    "D": "Only myelogram and molecular testing of the tumor"
                },
                "correct_answer": "A"
            }
        },
        {
            "19": {
                "question": "What is the treatment option for brain tumors that involves surgical removal of a tumor?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Chemotherapy",
                    "B": "Radiotherapy",
                    "C": "Surgery: craniotomy, excision",
                    "D": "Targeted therapy"
                },
                "correct_answer": "C"
            }
        },
        {
            "20": {
                "question": "What is the type of radiation therapy that uses protons rather than x-rays?",
                "options": {
                    "A": "Conventional radiation therapy",
                    "B": "3-dimensional conformal radiation therapy (3D-CRT)",
                    "C": "Intensity modulated radiation therapy (IMRT)",
                    "D": "Proton therapy"
                },
                "correct_answer": "D"
            }
        }
    ]
}]